our NATO army is already in the Kursk
наша натовская армия уже в Курской
region against Russia, 50 of the
области против России воюет 50
most powerful states are fighting against Russia, the army is in the
государств мощнейших государя армия в
Kursk region. Well, what do you think the
Курской области Ну а что ты думаешь это
Ukrainians are operating there, do you believe
украинцы там типа орудуют ты что веришь
in these
в эти
fairy tales
сказки
Hello Hello, where are you
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы
from in Simferopol? I understand how
откуда Симферополя понял как там
normal things are with you there
нормально с у вас
Well, we are trying to do this  give Ukraine
Ну мы стараемся это давать Украине
weapons so that yes I am from the USA Sacramento
оружие так чтобы да Я из США Сакраменто
we support Ukraine but we consider
мы поддерживаем Украину номы мы считаем
Crimea to be the territory of Ukraine so we
Крым территорию Украины поэтому мы
ask  Don’t beat the Ukrainians too much, we
просим украинцев сильно не лупить мы там
only hit military targets there, and
бьём только по военным объектам а
Belgorod Bryansk is just in short, godless,
Белгород Брянск просто Короче безбожно
so don’t worry, everything
так что Вы не переживайте с вами всё
will be fine,
будет хорошо
no, it’s calm, it’s occupying and everything will be
нет спокойно де оккупирует и всё будет
okay. What are your hopes for how long
окей Какие ваши надежды на то сколько
Crimea can
сможет Крым
hold out? Yes, listen, we can
продержаться да Ну слушайте мы можем
listen  as much as you want Well, in Kherson they also
слушать сколько угодно Ну в Херсоне тоже
said so, in the Kharkov region they
так говорили вон в Харьковской области
said so in Kursk they also said
так говорили в Курске говорили тоже та
what the Kursk region is like And now Oops, good,
какой Курская область А теперь Опа хоро
you are a US citizen and from
вы гражданин США и с из
already  I have citizenship in a year By the way, it
уже имею гражданство через года Кстати
will be fine for me to live in the
дто будет моего проживания в
USA You probably communicate
США прекрасно вы общаетесь наверняка с
with US citizens The USA I communicate with citizens of
гражданами США США я с гражданами это
Russia My parents remain in Rostov
России общаюсь У меня родители в Ростове
No, I’m talking about US citizens
остались Да нет я про граждан США говорю
Prim I’m a US citizen Yes, well, how do you communicate with them?  I do
Прим Я гражданин США Да ну вот вы с ними
n’t think they have an opinion Why did a
какое у них мнение мне каже не Почему
hundred actively vote for Trump
активно ста за трам голосовали трампа
because uh Why didn’t the majority vote for Biden
потому что ээ Почему за байдена не
you know because Biden
знаете потому что байден очень мало
helped Ukraine very little We think that Russia
помогал Украине У нас считают что Россия
Well Russia is well  the main
Ну Россия - это ж главный
geopolitical enemy of the United States since the
геополитический враг США ещё со времён
Cold War. Yes, that’s why Biden has
Холодной войны Да поэтому байдену
a claim that ONT and he, more precisely, well, from my
претензия что ОНТ и он точнее ну с моей
side, the United States is the most geopolitical Enemy,
стороны США самый геополитический Враг
well, yes, so we understand, look, we
ну да Вот и мы понимаем смотрите мы
understand, Reagan Reagan was a
понимаем вот Рейган Рейган был
Republican,
республиканец
just like Trump, he destroyed the Soviet
тоже как и Трамп он развалил Советский
Union, that is  defeated the Soviet Union in the
Союз то есть победил Советский Союз в
Cold War and we now believe
холодной войне и мы сейчас мы считаем
that Trump Yes
что Трамп Да
Donald he will defeat the Russian Federation
Дональд он победит Российскую Федерацию
because the result of Reagan was
потому что результатом рейгана был
the collapse of the Soviet Union the result of
распад Советского Союза результатом
Trump will be  collapse of the Russian
трампа будет распад Российской
Federation Well, it’s hard to say Why
Федерации Ну сложно сказать Ну почему
how many dollars do you already have there, 104 or 105
сколько у вас уже там доллар 104 или 105
today? It
сегодня ну Россию саму Россию как
seems to me impossible to destroy Russia itself as a power.
державу развалить Мне кажется невозможно
Why did the Soviet Union collapse and it
Почему Советский Союз развалили а он
was a more complex
сложнее был
power? The Soviet Union Yes, they collapsed I
держава Советский Союз Да развалили
agree, well, this is a great achievement of
Согласен это ну это большое достижение
the USA Well  concerns Russia It seems to me that
США Ну что касается России Мне кажется
this is impossible a little different T the
это невозможно немножко другое Т
ideological concept is
идеологическое понятие есть такое
Russian with Russians to
русский с русскими
fight than this in the
воевать чем это в
Soviet Union is the same thing ideologically, the
Советском же самое идеологически
Soviet Union is, well, this is Well, you
Советский Союз - это ну это Ну вы же
understand  this is the council of the Soviet
понимаете это совет советских тических
republics, everyone wanted Freedom, everyone didn’t
республик все захотели Свободы все не
understand perestroika, it was
поняли перестройки тут было это
universal, so look, so you have the
вселенское так смотрите Так у вас же то
same thing now, you have the Tatars, the Bashkorts, too, the
же самое сейчас есть татары башкорт тоже
Republics have everything, everything is according to the same
Республики есть всё всё по той же
scheme. No, it won’t work. Yes, everything will work according to the
схеме Нет нет не прокатит Да всё по той
same scheme. Look  now after
же схеме прокатит Смотри сейчас после
Putin, Putin is old. But now will he
Путина Путин старенький Да сейчас ли его
either be overthrown or installed just like
либо свергнут либо поставят так же как
Gorbachev, who will do
Горбачёва который будет делать
perestroika and that’s all? Well, if you’re so
перестройку и всё А ну если ты так
far away, maybe  Well, look
далеко на пекти может ну так смотри
really what’s being done, it’s the same
реально что делается это ж тот же самый
guy, Brezhnev went to Afghanistan Yes, he
тип вот в Брежнев зашёл в Афганистан Да
went to Afghanistan then Brezhnev
зашёл в Афганистан потом Брежнев
was installed once Then they installed
поставили раз раз Потом поставили
Gorbachev, they did
Горбачёва сделали
perestroika in Europe, I understand what you
перестроечная Европы я я понял о чём ты
’re talking about, but the Brix countries
говоришь но а страны Брикс тебе ни о чём
don’t tell you anything  And what do country Brix say
не говорят А что говорят страный Брикс
that country Brix seriously serious
что страный Брикс серьёзно серьёзные
guys ST countries countries Brix trading
ребята СТ страны страны Брикс торговые
partners USA everything is
партнёры США всё
fine Well, what is a military alliance
нормально Ну а что такое военный Союз
signed with China and what is a
подписанный с Китаем ю те какой Какой
military alliance with  You
военный союз с Китаем у вас
have signed by China You have a military union
подписанный У вас есть военный Союз
signed with Armenia Belarus
подписанный с Арменией беларусью
Kazakhstan Kyrgyzstan Tajikistan
Казахстаном Киргизстана таджикистаном
is called the CSTO other military alliances
называется одкб других военных союзов у
you do
вас
n’t have Moscow Minsk Beijing there is no such
нет Москва минс Пекин нет такого
agreement show show military
соглашения покажи покажи военное
agreement What kind of agreement Well, how am I for
соглашение Какое соглашение Ну ну как я
now you know that I’m not yet Well
тебе пока ты знаешь что я те не пока Ну
like Look what an agreement if China
как Смотри какое соглашение если Китай
sells weapons components to Ukraine
продаёт Украине комплектующие для
Russia continues to supply gas
оружие Россия продолжает поставлять газ
and that Tae is not there, that is, look The fact is
и что Тае нет то есть смотри Дело в том
that China does not  is a military ally of Russia
что Китай не есть союзником России
Not yet, we are not at war not yet, so
военным Пока нет мы не воюем ещё нет так
you say that there is some kind of agreement
ты говоришь что там какой-то договор
Belarus China has its own war, so far there
Белорусь Китай есть сво войны пока-то
is no such thing Well, as you already have a
нет таковой Ну как у вас уже на
war on the territory of the Russian Federation,
территории Российской Федерации война
Kursk region, everything is nuclear doctrine
Курская область всё ядерная доктрина
blah blah Well, okay  but they didn’t declare war.
бла-бла Ну хорошо но войну объявили нет
So why declare it if you can, look,
Так а зачем Объявлять если можно смотри
we are Americans through Ukraine. Yes, our
мы американцы через Украину Да наше
proxy is seizing the territory of the
прокси делаем захват территории
Russian Federation. Why should we declare
Российской Федерации Зачем нам Объявлять
war? Belarus is obliged to support
войну Белоруссия обязана поддержать
Russia and Beijing, too, where is it?  look at
Россию и Пекин тоже где вот смотри на
your Kursk region they attacked you captured for
вашу курскую область напали захватили
a month you can’t recapture it where is Beijing where is
меся не можете её отбить где Пекин где
Belarus where are they
Белорусь где они
all well you want it to come to this And
все ну ты хочешь чтобы до этого дошло И
so look you came up with some kind of no
так смотри ты придумал какой-то никакого
agreement Yes with Beijing so that it
договора Да с Пекином для того чтобы он
would defend Russia if it doesn’t attack no
защищал Россию если оно не нападут нету
Show me Well, how I’ll show you Well, what’s
Покажи Ну как я тебе покажу Ну как
the name of the treaty, what’s the
называется договор как Союз
name of the Union? Moscow Minsk Beijing I’ll give it to you
называется Москва Минск Пекин я тебе
now just for fun Google it
сейчас давай ради интереса Погугли
Come on Moscow Minsk
Давай Москва Минск
Beijing buy a plane ticket
Пекин купить билет на самолёт
gives out Look I  beat Moscow Minsk Beijing
выдаёт Смотри я бил Москва Минск Пекин
everything that Minsk Beijing gives out buy
всё что выдаёт Минск Пекин купить билета
tickets tickets Minsk
билеты Минск
Beijing agreement Come on
Пекин договор Давай
agreement agreement Moscow Minsk
договор договор Москва Минск
Beijing no no no
Пекин нет
Well no, I typed the agreement into Google
нет Ну нету я вбил в Google договор
Moscow Minsk Beijing there is no such
Москва Минск Пекин нету такого ни одного
message, can you find me and tell me
сообщение можешь мне найти и сказать
that Well, [ __ ] Well, God forbid  it won’t come to that,
что Ну бля Ну дай Бог до этого не
so there are no agreements that
дойдёт так нету никаких соглашений что
China should be
там Китай должен
conjugated there, the only comrades-in-arms
спрягается единственные Соратники кое ва
were the CSTO and the Military Union, it’s
были это одкб да ш военный Союз это как
like there is NATO, but there is  CSTO as an analogue of the
бы вот есть НАТО а есть одкб как аналог
Warsaw Pact which the
Варшавского договора который был у
USSR had, allies in the CSTO should be included in the event of an
СССР союзники по одкб должны в случае
attack on Russia. This is
нападения на Россию были включиться это
Belarus
Белорусь
Kazakhstan Tajikistan Kyrgyzstan and
Казахстан Таджикистан Кыргызстан и
Armenia, so they are all clearly not Uzbekistan is
Армения так они все чётко не Узбекистан
not included in the WKB.
не входит вкб
So they clearly took or Russia to
Вот они чётко взяли или Россию куда
hell with the
подальше
Armed Forces Well, not all, well all  and which of them which
ВС Ну не все ну все а кто кто из них кто
of them
из них
supported Belarus not Belarus, look
поддержал Беларусь не Беларусь смотри
Belarus even forced Russia to withdraw
Беларусь даже заставила Россию вывести
troops from
войска со своей
wait for your territory, Belarus is the
территории подожди Беларусь - это ну
only military ally of the RO e No, it’s not
единственный военный союзник ро е Нет не
military, look, I’m going to stop at all,
воен смотрите Берусь перестала вообще
it’s not giving up its territory for takeoffs, not for
она не Дат свою територию взлётов не для
shelling, there’s not a single Russian
обстрела всё ни одного российского
soldier in Belarus, they’ve
солдата нет в Беларуси
even been withdrawn, no, everything is a joint
даже вывели нет всё есть совместное
exercise Yes, the exercise is an exercise, an exercise with
учение Да учение - это учение учение со
everyone is like there and what Well so and what well
всеми есть типа там и что Ну так и что
wait Well so what Well why Well what Well
ну подожди Ну и что Ну к чему Ну чему Ну
look I say that here is the result
смотри я говорю что вот результат 6
August 6, 24  year, Ukrainian troops began the
августа 24 года украинские войска начали
liberation of the Kursk region from the
освобождение Курской области от
Kremlin occupiers, because of the Kremlin
кремлёвских оккупантов изза кремлёвских
occupiers, no one has stood up for
оккупантов никто не вступился уже
how many more than x months, soon it
сколько уже больше х месяцев скоро 4
will be 4 months And no one can do anything to
месяца будет И никто ничего не может
Ukraine What is the Kremlin occupier,
Украине Что такое Кремлёвские оккупант
what is it anyway, well, the Kremlin
это что такое вообще это ну Кремлёвский
Yes, yes, this is the Kremlin o  which
Да да это есть Кремлёвская о которая
captured the territories of the former Kievan Rus
захватила территории бывшей Руси
and the Golden Horde, now
Да и Золотой Орды вот сейчас
these territories are being liberated
освобождаются эти территории
from not only the Mongols  Kazakhs, Tatars of all sorts
у не только монголы казахи татары всякие
Yes, now I understand, well, the theory is of course
Да сечас Понятно ну теория конечно
interesting And you Indians are there for their
интересно А вас индейцы там за свои
territories No, the Indians and I
территории Нет мы с индейцами нормально
live normally We live normally
Живём нормально
community Nunu You understand this is a lie
сообщество нуну Ты же понимаешь это бре
Mongols Moscow, the
монголы Москва
fact that the USA is Kazakh is already clear Yes,
то что США казахов это уже понятно Да
they are there in the sense that they are not Kazakhs, look
они там уже в смысле не казахи смотри
Kazakhs  Yes, they have always been a free
казахи Да они всегда были вольным
people. Yes, the Russian Empire has not yet
народом Да пока Российская империя не
seized part of their territories. Yes,
захватила часть ихних территорий Да
now there is a process of returning
сейчас идёт процесс возвращения
historical justice to the Kazakhs, like
исторической справедливости казахи как и
others  Turkic peoples are returning their
другие тюркские народы возвращают свои
ancestral lands Orenburg - by the way, the
исконные земли Оренбург - это кстати
primordial Kazakh Land will also be
исконная казахская Земля тоже будет
returned to Kazakhstan as a result of the
возвращена Казахстану по результатам
division of the Russian state That's all
раздела российского государст Вот и вс у
my aunt lives there by the way super
меня там тётка живёт кстати супер
will move to
переедет в
Moscow Well why will Moscow move to me
Москву Ну почему Москву ко мне переедет
in Crimea where are you from Crimea you from
в Крым куда так ты с Крыма ты с Крыма
You will also move to Moscow from Crimea.
тоже в Москву переедешь
Why, why would you be shorter for us in
Почему А зачем ты нам будешь короче в
American Crimea? Are
американском Крыму
you in American Crimea?
Ты в американском Крыму Ну
Well, in general  they will all
да вообще се оче
come out of Crimea Yes, there will be an
во выйдут из Крыма Да там будет по
American military base in
американская военная база в
Sevastopol in accordance with the agreements with Ukraine as a Guarantor of stability in the
Севастополе как Гарант стабильности в
region Well,
регионе Ну
yes, what’s
да а что тут
wrong with that But in Chernomor there will be two
такого Бут в но в Черномор будут две
Russian two of these American military
российски две этих американские военные
bases Sevastopol Novorossiysk,
базы Севостополь Новороссийск
it’s normal and of course Take  for such
нормально можно и конечно Взять за такие
you will take it
возьмёте вы возьмёте
yes Well I see Well these are unreal things
да Ну понятно Ну это ж нереальные вещи
Why unreal I agree look at
Почему нереальные согласен смотри
unreal things - this is to beat off
нереальные вещи - это отбить русских
Russians from near Kyiv These were unreal things and everything else is already there Kherson Kharkov Crimea Sevastopol you, of course, have coveted such things, I’ll accept them Well, because, well, this can’t happen Why can’t it, well, because you don’t have enough spirit, and there’s enough spirit for missiles that’s all, we’re not Americans. Yes, we gave permission to hit the territory of the Russian Federation, now the missile is just like now look, like now I’ll slam the Crimean Bridge, Yes, I’ll slam the railway connection and that’s it  the military will be in a trap that everything is so
всё военные будут в ловушке что всё так
and that everything is nothing, I’ll blow a couple of power plants
а что всё ничего пару электростанций
and in short there’s all this stuff Well then,
бахну и короче там весь этот сй Ну тогда
well Then we’ll have to destroy the entire
ну Тогда придётся уничтожить всё
population of Crimea What is the population of Crimea,
население Крыма Какое население Крыма
look at the Crimea, the Germans took Yes, Bolbochan
смотри Крым немцы брали Да болбочан брал
took everything without problems Crimea Why
все брали без проблем Крым Зачем
destroy the population of Crimea, look at the
население Крыма уничтожать смотри
Russians  the troops are being taken away, they're running away, yeah, they're
российские войска уводят убегают Да ээ с
running away with them. Those who collaborated with the
ними убегают Те кто сотрудничал с
Russian occupiers, there's
российскими оккупантами там полисмен
all sorts of policemen like these  policemen Prosecutors
всякие типа вот эти полицаи Прокуроры
judges who doesn't run away Yes everyone who
судьи кто не убежит Да все кто
cooperated will be convicted for
сотрудничал будут осуждены да
nothing According to your theory I'm the same flag as
ра По твоей теории Я такой же флаг как и
you I'll hang myself on the wall or whatever's in
ты повешаю себя на стене или что в
my head Well yes yes you'll hang it and what Well
голове Ну да да повесишь а что Ну
you'll hang it too You'll still say I
этоже ты повесишь ещё будешь говорить я
was against the occupation Just  I was silent
был против оккупации Просто я молчал
because they weren’t mocking us here. You
Потому что тут издевались над нами не Ты
’ll even go to parades
ещё на парады будешь выходить
and say that I’m for the
даже и будешь говорить что я за с
rainbow flag, you’ll walk and say
радужным флагом будешь ходить и говорить
No, you’ve got something mixed up with us  there
Да нет ты что-то перепутал у нас такой
won’t be such a topic, but in any case, I’m telling you
темы не будет да по-любому я тебе говорю
in Sevastopol you will still hold these festivals in
в Севастополе будешь ещё эти фестивали
any way. Well, I’m telling you with my
проводить по-любому Ну я же тебе говорю
bare hands, just who are you
голыми руками только кого ты голыми
looking with your bare hands from Kherson when the
руками смотри из Херсона когда
Russian troops ran away, where are all these
российские войска убежали где эти все
stranglers with their
душители
hands from the Kursk region when they ran away
руками из Курской области когда убежали
Russian troops came NATO Our
российские войска пришли натовские Наши
troops And who is where these stranglers with their hands
войска А кто там где эти душители руками
All of
Все
you except your own there with your hands
ты разве что своего там руками
in that’s all yes yes yes you blew it like that
в вот и всё да да да аче ты так продул
Well look Agree that  Russia is a
Ну смотри Согласись что Россия
technologically backward power
технологически отсталая держава по
compared to America and it
сравнению с Америкой и она ничего не
cannot provide anything technology that you are
может предоставить технологи что что вы
producing nothing at all, so we have always
выпускает вообще ничего так мы всегда
been
были
from and the Soviet Union has collapsed
от и Советский Союз развалили
America has collapsed the Russian Empire
Америка развалила Российскую империю
America has collapsed the Soviet Union and
Америка развалила Советский Союз и
now there is the third stage of the collapse of the
сейчас идёт третий этап распада
so-called Russian Empire, that
Российской Империи так называемой то
is  The Russian Federation must
есть Российская Федерация должна
return to the borders of 1240
вернуться к границам 1240
Uh-huh And what And what will happen to you Look
Угу А что А что с тобой будет Смотри
when If you don’t leave after
когда Если ты не уедешь после
the de-occupation of Crimea  before you have time to leave, there
деоккупации Крыма не успеешь уехать да
will be a filtration, yes, that is, they will
будет проведена фильтрация да то есть
look at you if you collaborated with the
посмотрят если ты сотруд
police
полицейским
state, this is what it is. You
государстве такое это такое Ты же не ты
didn’t help kill people there, you didn’t judge
не помогал людей убивать там ты не судил
you, you
ты не
weren’t, well, you just know,
был ну просто знаешь там будут коса на
your neighbors will look at you crossly and that’s it.
тебя смотреть твои соседи и всё А так
like you’ll go to all these parades
типа будешь ходить на эти на парады
like for the independence of Crimea and still
всякие типа за независимость Крыма и всё
Crimea returned to
ти Крым вернулся в
Ukraine Bro, you’re a little confused, how can I
Украины Братан ты немножко не ну как
explain it to you Well, yes, you’ve
бы как тебе объяснить Ну у тебя Да ты в
been living there in the USA for a long time  most
США там живёшь уже долго скорее всего
likely, probably already, well, 18 years in 2 years, it will be like
наверное уже ну 18 лет через 2 года буде
that Yes, and probably all these Memories are alien to you
дто Да и наверное тебе чужды эти все
Memories there My parents
там какие Воспоминания У меня родители в
live in Rostov, I communicate with them every
Ростове живут я с ними общаюсь каждый
month Yes, you interpret it all
месяц Да ты и трактует это всё
differently
по-другому
Well, you and I are bipolar people  absolutely
Ну мы с тобой биполярные люди абсолютно
what kind of people are Well, what are you talking about is
какие люди Ну то о чём ты говоришь это
this, well, this is your theory, of course it’s
это ну это твоя теория конечно она
interesting, well, it does exist, but
интересная ну она имеет место быть но
to say that people here will surrender there
утверждать что здесь люди сдадутся там
or something else But this is big In the
или что-то там ещё Но это большой В
sense that they will surrender and run away Well  as you look, it’s
смысле сдадутся убегут Ну как смотри всё
very simple Kursk Okay, there was
ж очень очень просто Курск Ладно там
a wing And Kursk Like, they attacked Kursk
крыл А Курск Типа так на Курск напали вы
so you ran to defend Kursk, you didn’t run
что побежали защищать Курск не побежали
You need it, really, so you didn’t
Вам он нужен правда
go to defend Kursk and Dzhankoy,
выж не пошли защищать Курск и Джанкой
no one will defend and
никто не будет защищать и Севастополь
no one will
никто не будет
defend Sevastopol Well, what will you do?  do Well,
защищать Ну что ты будешь делать Ну
American Soldiers will come there
придут американские Солдаты туда
Peacekeepers And that’s it And what are you going to
Миротворцы И всё И что ты будешь
do? You’ll climb up and throw a Molotov cocktail
делать полезешь коктейль Молотова кидать
at them No, I’ll just die and that’s all, just like
на них Да нет я погибну просто и всё как
you’ll die
ты погибнешь
swimming across  Kerch
переплывая Керченский
Bay No, defending your home How Well,
залив Нет защищая свой дом Как
how do I know how What kind of
Ну откуда я знаю как Что за
questions are you, what are these your fantasies or that
вопросы ты что это твои фантазии или что
I won’t Who is stopping you?
я ж не буду Кто кто тебе мешает Ты же
Look, you see that now NATO
смотри Ты видишь что сейчас натовские
troops are waging a war against the Russian
войска ведут войну против Российской
Federation. Why aren’t you going to
Федерации Почему ты сейчас не идёшь
defend now?  my
защитить свой
house, so I protect it
дом так я его защищаю
like Well, I’m at home,
как Ну я нахожусь дома
that is, Your house is just your
то есть Твой дом это просто твоя
apartment
квартира
Yes, yes, that is, not Russia. That is, I
Да ну да то есть не Росси То есть я
understand that you will only protect
понимаю что ты будешь защищать только
your apartment but not the Russian Federation.
свою квартиру но не Российскую Федерацию
Yes,
Да
wait,
подожди
there are people who  they are fighting Yes, there are not
есть люди которые воюют Да их не хватает
enough of them. There are not enough of them because look, our
Не хватает потому что смотри наша
NATO army is already in the Kursk
натовская армия уже в Курской
region against Russia, 50 states are fighting
области против России воюет 50
Monet's army in the Kursk region. Well, what do you
Моне года армия в Курской области Ну что
think, it’s the Ukrainians who are operating there, do
ты думаешь это украинцы там типа орудуют
you believe in these
ты что веришь в эти
fairy tales? That is, these are your Companions
сказки То есть это ну ваши Соратники
In short  what is it
Короче как это
called they participate yes Well of course
называется они участвуют да Ну конечно
well not officially it’s based on the principle they are
ну не официально это по принципу их там
not there like Zena little men you understand
нет как зены человечки ты понимаешь
the war on sales yes well just why should we
война на даж да ну просто зачем нам
declare war if we can yes  under
Объявлять войну если мы можем да под
the guise that it seems like the Ukrainians are seizing the
видом вроде как это украинцы захватывают
Kursk region, there are NATO
курскую область там натовские
instructors, the troops are all Mercenaries and that’s all, and there are
инструктора войска все Наёмники и всё и
not enough conscripts there,
не хватает там кого каких-то срочников
I watched the video from us, that is, in
бросали я смотрел видео у нас то есть по
fact, Well, based on your words, we are already
сути Ну исходя из твоих слов мы уже
at war with your country Yes, no no  you are at war
воюем с твоей страной Да не не вы воюете
with our country And our country is at war with
с нашей страной А наша страна воюет с
you on the territory of America there is no
вами на на территории Америки нет
war, but on the territory of Russia there is an understanding
войны а на территории России есть понят
on the territory of America there would never be a
на территории Америки никогда не бы
war other than a civil one, but on the
войны кроме гражданской вот а на
territory of Russia there is now a War and you are
территории России сейчас идёт Война и ты
not  you are defending Russia, the truth is, that
не защищаешь Россию правда то есть то
is, the United States is now at war with the Russian
есть США сейчас воюет с Российской
Federation
Федерацией
Yes, and it is fighting very smartly Yes, so that the
Да причём Очень умно воюет Да так чтобы
international community can see that it seems
Международное сообщество видело вроде
like the United States is not at war Yes, officially we are
как США не воюет Да официально нас там
not there So it is there, well, the United States has been at war with the
нет Так она там ну США воевала с
Russian Federation It turns out for
Российской Федерации получается уже
how many years 60 yes
сколько лет 60 да
And  now you think they’ll pull it out. Well,
И сейчас ты думаешь они вытащат Ну
of course, look. They pulled it out in the
конечно смотри Они же вытащили В
ninety-first year, but this is against
девяносто первом году да это против
such a machine as the Soviet Union. And look,
такой машины как Советский Союз А смотри
in the ninety-first year  what did they
В девяносто первом что сделали от вас
tear Lithuania, Latvia, Estonia,
оторвали Литву Латвию Эстонию там
Ukraine, Kazakhstan and others away from you so that you would
Украину Казахстан и другие чтобы у вас
n’t have such a mobilization resource
не было мобилизационного ресурса такого
for war? They waited 30 years longer,
для войны Всё дальше подождали 30 лет
digest, they degraded your
переварите деградировали вашу
industry. But after all, what
промышленность Да всё-таки что Советский
could the Soviet Union do? And now Russia
Союз Да мог делать А что сейчас Россия
can’t even damn it  Tan Armata put a
даже не может блин тан армата поставить
test model on this at the front and they
на этот на фронт испытательный образец и
can’t do that anymore, that is, the
всё и то больше не могуть всё то есть
Soviet Union launched people into
Советский Союз запускал там людей в
space there, dogs into space, launched whatever
космос собак в космос запускал что
you want to do, they were afraid of him,
хочешь делать его боялись
yes  you see, you see how hard it is to be Russian
да видиш видишь как тяжело быть русским
Well, let’s fight
Ну поборемся
against your Great
против вашей Великой
Power Well, why don’t you fight, you see,
державы Ну как ты же не борешься видишь
you sit and are at home
ты сиди и дома ри
and died in the Kursk region and they are
гиб в Курской области да и попадают в
captured, you sit and you will sit like that until the
плен ты сидишь и ты так будешь сидеть до
end of the war Listen, well, of course you are also pouring
конца войны Слушай ну ты тоже конечно
that  What about you? Well, you are a Patriot of the USA. Well,
льешь ту А ты что Ну ты Патриот США Ну
you are participating. So, look, there is
ты участвуешь Так у нас смотри на
no war on the territory of the United States, we have a
территории США войны нету у нас есть
contract army. Well, why are you
контрактная армия Ну а зачем ты меня
seeing me off? We have a contract army and from it
прово у нас контрактная армия и из неё
only a small part Yes with other
только маленькая часть Да с другими
NATO in this uh war in Russia everything
натовские в этой ээ войне в России всё
why are we all calm our life our
зачем мы все спокойны у нас жизнь у нас
alarms don’t turn on our missiles don’t
тревоги не включаются у нас ракеты не
fly and you have everything in Russia Well yes
летают а у вас в России есть и всё Ну да
yes And when Yes when I’m in the twenty-second
да И когда Да когда я в двадцать втором
year, too, I went out to talk, my
году тоже я выходил пообщаться у меня
relatives are in Rostov there and
родственники ж в Ростове там и
Odnoklassniki’s nicknames are what I’m saying
Одноклассники ники они з это я говорю
So don’t go to fight And they’re like that
Так что не идёте воевать А они такие Ну
Well, if there’s already a war on Russian territory
вот если будет на территории России уже
I’m saying this if you think Crimea
война Я говорю так если вы считаете рым
There and so on  Donetsk region of Russia
Там и так дальше Донецкая область России
Yes they Well, no, well, it doesn’t count But
Да они Ну вот нет ну это не считается Но
if I’m on the territory of true Russia and
если вот на территории истинной России и
I’m now taking a shorter course When the
я сейчас короче курс Когда вошли
Ukrainians entered Well, under the guise of NATO Ukrainians,
украинцы Ну под видом украинцев НАТО
I called ours. I have Sanya Prokhorov,
наши я позвонил У меня Саня Прохоров
a classmate, I say that he went to fight,
Одноклассник говорю что пошёл воевать он
well, like there’s
ну типа там
North Korean  the frost fell just like
северокорейское на мороз упали как и
you Well, of course, they probably
ты Ну понятное дело у них наверное дети
have children and a family and so on
есть и семья и так далее
Yes, here you are sitting l Wait, wait,
Да вот ты вот сидишь л Подожди подожди
look That is, it turns out that you all want
смотри То есть получается вы все хотите
to fight against  NATO and Ukraine Yes, but so
воевать против НАТО и Украины Да но
that someone else fights and not you
чтобы воевал кто-то другой а не вы
because you have children
потому что у вас дети
Yes no, wait Well, let’s
Да нет так подожди Ну давай
look at it Well, the conflict in general is
рассматривать Ну вот конфликт вообще
about What is it just look The conflict
из-за Чего это просто смотри Конфликт -
is a geopolitical
это геополитическое
confrontation between the United States and the Soviet
противостояние США и Советского
Union Well, that’s how she spends  your life is
Союза Ну так она тратит свою жизнь это
for spending your life on this, here you and I are
для тратить свою жизнь на эту вот мы с
communicating now Yes, you have a US flag there
тобой общаемся сейчас Да у тебя там флаг
and so on Well, I have to
США и так далее Ну я должен свою жизнь
lay down my life so that you sit here and continue to
положить чтобы ты тут сидел дальше с
communicate with others or Well, wait, I don’t
другими общался или Ну Так подожди я не
know We  Well, we are waging a war on the territory of the
знаю Мы ж мы ведём войну на территории
Russian Federation. Yes, if we
Российской Федерации Да если б у нас
had, for example, Mexico or Cuba
была например Мексика или куба на нас
attacked us. Yes, you definitely don’t. Well, your
напала Да точно не ведёшь Ну твоя
power, which you recognized, my power is
держава которую ты признал моя держава
waging. Yes, I am a citizen of the United States,
ведёт Да я гражданин Соединённых Штатов
yes I am and I am proud of it and I will say this
да я ц и я горжусь этим и я скажу так
my state Yes, it wouldn’t allow
моя держава Да не допустила бы чтобы её
someone to squeeze out even a meter of earth, they would immediately
хотя бы метр земли кто-то отжал сразу бы
raise the third US Marine Corps
подняли третий корпус морской пехоты США
And everything would fall out And now Russia, what did
Да и выпали бы всё А сейчас Россия что
we look at, they showed us it there
там мы смотрели нам показывали это там
nut something was shot Russia is showing
орех что-то выстрелили Россия показывает
that some kind of missile is a power on on on on the
что какую-то ракету держава на на на
rights of strong people around the world Yes,
правах сильных людей по всему миру Да
my power my power on the right of
моя держава моя держава на Праве
the strong, yes you are right, we are a superpower, we
сильного да ты прав мы сверхдержава мы
can afford to enter the Kursk
можем позволить себе зайти в курскую
region under the guise of a Ukrainian and let the people
область под видом украинца и пу людей
go  Yes, yes, these are our geopolitical
уть Да да да это наши геополитические
interests Well, okay, Russia too Look, and it
интересы Ну хорошо и Россия Смотри и
turns out Putin can’t do anything
получается Путин ничего не может сделать
Well, we are defending ourselves,
Ну мы защищаемся
our system Well, how do you defend yourself if,
наше системы Ну как ты защищается если
look, your country is in danger And you are all
смотри ваша страна в опасности А вы все
sitting here My classmate Sanya  Prokhorov
сидите Мой одноклассник Саня Прохоров
doesn’t do anything, you’re not doing anything, you’re
ничего не делает ты ничего не делаеш
hooked on your Odnoklass because
зацепился за своего Однокласс потому что
he’s been carrying a heavy metal since his second year, and
он с д второго года зку зку таскал А
now he’s already sitting quietly. No, you
сейчас и уже сидит тихонько Нет ну вы
people all over the world, you agree. Well,
людей по всему миру Ты же согласен Ну
of course, we’re a superpower, we can
конечно да мы сверхдержава мы можем себе
afford it and
позволить и
now I’m having a blast  Yes, look, we
сейчас кайфую Да смотри раньше мы это
used to do this all over the world, but we couldn’t
делали по всему миру но мы не могли это
do it in the Russian Federation, you’re
делать в Российской Федерации ты
enjoying yourself. Why are you looking because
кайфуешь А почему ты смотри потому что у
we have a professional army that
нас есть профессиональная армия которая
does this and look from  our
этим занимается и смотри из нашей
professional army is only a small
профессиональной армии только маленькой
limited contingent fighting now in
ограниченный контингент воюет сейчас в
Russia you have good weapons
России у вас есть хорошее оружие армии у
you don’t have a professional army Well, look at
вас нет профессионально Ну как смотри
the army - it is people and weapons Yes and
армия - это есть люди и оружие Да и
their management If our effective
управление ими Если наша эффективная
army can not there how many there are about a
армия может не там сколько там около
thousand people of our soldiers can
тысячи человек наших солдат могут
capture the Kursk region Yes, yours Well, that
захватить курскую область Да вашу Ну это
means our army is
значит наша армия
professional Yeah
профессиональная Угу
Agree, look In the whole world, the
Согласись смотри Во всм мире действует
rule of force is now strong, the USA and no
право силы сейчас сильные США и это
one will say anything to a superpower, and
сверх державе никто ничего не скажет и
Putin Yes, having nuclear weapons Yes, how was he
Путин Да имея ядерное оружие Да как он
when the Kursk region was taken that he
когда курскую область взяли что он
did it, that’s enough [ __ ] touching Putin, if
сделал да хватит Путина трогать бля если
it weren’t for Putin, we wouldn’t have been around for a long time. Well,
б не Путин нам бы вообще уже давно не Ну
look. So what, what can he do,
смотри Так а что что он может сделать
draw a red line for
красную линию нарисовать у
himself? Well, he’s doing something.
себя Ну что-то делает
Well, what can you oppose to
Ну а что что вы можете противопоставить
the United States? It’s
США вот
real. Why do you need this?  I
реально Зачем тебе это нужно вот вот
can’t understand and this is what you’re
понять не могу и вот ты вот чего
proving:
доказываешь
You’re a citizen of a superpower Yes, I’m a citizen
Ты гражданин сверхдержавы Да я гражданин
of a superpower yes Well, what do I want? I want
сверхдержавы да Ну и что я я хочу я хочу
my parents in Rostov to also live
чтобы мои родители в Ростове тоже жили
like in this superpower. I want
как в этой сверхдержав Я хочу
this in  I live in Rostov Yes, they’re still in
чтобы это в Ростове живу Да они ещё в
Rostov. My dad has a 20 ruble pension, that’s
Ростове у меня У бати 20 руб пенсия это
ridiculous. 200 dollars
смешно 200 долларов
less, too. You’re chasing away.
меньше тоже Прогоняешь
Well, you’re a US citizen and you have
Какую Ну что ты гражданин США и у вас
a superpower. Well, they don’t know. Mom
сверхдержава Ну да не знают Мама меня
will support me. Dad will support me a little. He’s a little
поддержит папа немножко он там немножко
pro-Putin there, but he’s already thinking.  already
за Путина но уже он задумался он уже
thinking by the way, he was already in he was so
задумался кстати он уже в он был такой
busy Now he looks that somehow everything is
зати Сейчас он смотрит что как-то всё
so rosy and so What are you Well, well, well, well,
так радужно так А что ты Ну ну так ну
focus on your family  you have only one life,
сосредоточься на семье у тебя жизнь одна
you are meddling in this geopolitics and who is I who is I
ты лезешь в эту геополитику и А кто мне
who is not we are just deciding I
кто мне нет мы как раз решаем я
voted I just went to the elections I was
голосовал я как раз ходил на выборы я
campaigning Yes because he promised that
агитировать Да потому что он обещал что
he would stop this war will force Putin to
он остановит эту войну заставит Путина
sign the Peace Agreement Yes he won’t He doesn’t
подписать Мирное со Да не сделает Он не
decide  neither Trump, look already further,
решает ни Трамп де смотри уже уже далее
look Trump has not yet been inaugurated, has not
смотри Трамп ещё не стал инаугурацию не
already passed Ukraine was allowed to fire
прошёл уже Украине разрешили бить
long-range missiles,
дальнобойные ракетами
you know, you understand that
тный человек ты же понимаешь что рулят
some corporations are in charge that sell
какие-то корпорации которые продают
Coca-Cola diapers and so on, these are the
кока-колу подгузники и так далее вот эти
types
типы
that monopolists earn money,
которые монополисты зарабатывают бабки
this is an irreversible process and Based on
этот необратимый процесс и Исходя из
this, the whole
этого вся
life of ordinary people is simply
жизнь обычных людей она просто
leveled out for them, it is
нивелируется для них она
neither And that we will be proud of this, some
ни И что мы будем этом Горди какой-то
country, a country,
страной страна
look, My country protects its own in this way
у смотри Моя страна так защищает свои
geopolitical interests My country
геополитические интересы Моя страна
establishes the world order, yes In
устанавливает мировой миропорядок да Для
order for you to know, this is how
того чтобы было знаешь вот как убирает
Russia removes all lawless people, the
всех беспредельщиков Россия государство
lawless state of the USA introduces normal
беспредельщик США вносит нормальные
laws in those countries where they are coming
законы в те страны куда приходят вот
now Russian Federation yes  In the
сейчас Российская Федерация да В
ninety-first year, the
девяносто первом году нормально
Soviet Union collapsed normally, they gave you
развалили Советский Союз поставили вам
Yeltsin. Yes, they installed Yeltsin, they already did
Ельцина Да поставили Ельцина делали уже
normal democratic processes there.
там нормально демократические процессы
No, you took it, turned it around, well, it’s all a carrot
Да нет вы взяли повернули ну всё это
and stick method; in the 0s they
метод кнута и пряника вам в 0х давали
gave you a
окорочка Это был пряник сейчас вам дают
piece of meat.  they'll ruin it again
кнут потом немножко вас развалит снова
they'll give you a chicken leg to calm me down, I don't understand
дадут окорочка чтобы успоко не понял о
what I'm talking about, I already understood that Well, I
чём я говорю я уже понял что Ну я
understand perfectly well what you're talking about, how
прекрасно понимаю о чём ты говоришь как
they ruined the country, we survived it  this is
развалили страну это пережили уже это
already a passed stage Yes, they tried to bend it,
уже пройденный этап Да пытались нагнуть
holding it, they destroyed it Yes adj Yeltsin lived
держа её развалили Да прил Ельцин жили
T the whole world laughed, a great country at
Т смеялся весь мир великая страна над
which the whole world laughed, what in the end Are you
которой смеялся весь мир что по итогу Ты
trying to prove that you are great
что пытаешься доказать что ты великий
Nagi Yes, I am a citizen, I am a citizen of a Great
Наги Да я гражда я гражданин Великой
country that is now bending the
страны которая нагибает сейчас
Russian Federation Yes  I’m pleased with that.
Российскую Федерацию Да мне это приятно
What are
А что
you saying, your parents are in Rostov and
ты говоришь у тебя родители в Ростове и
you’re pleased that you’re supporting your
тебе приятно что ты нагибаешь свою
country? Yes, not my country. My country is not the
страну Да не не мою стра Моя страна не
Soviet Union in which I was born. It’s
Советский Союз в котором я родился его
already  there is no The country in which I was born
уже нету Той страны в которой я родился
My country is the United States of
Моя страна - это Соединённые Штаты
America, a free country I don’t understand your
Америки свободная ра Я не пойму твой
patriotism, this is what it decides in general You,
патриотизм это что он решает вообще Ты
how is your relationship with me in general I
как вообще твоё отношение с мне Мне
like Look, I have it, as if I
нравится Смотри у меня есть как бы я
was born in the Soviet Union, too, it
родился в Советском Союзе тоже э
drives me away  I’ll explain to you Look, I
прогоняет я объясню тебе Смотри Я
was born in the Soviet Union Yes, I was
родился в Советском Союзе Да у меня меня
brought up on the idea that you need to be a Great
воспитали на том что нужно быть Великой
Power to seize capture Unfortunately,
державой захватывать захват К сожалению
the Soviet Union turned out to be a dummy of the
Советский Союз оказался пустышкой
Russian Federation I have now chosen the
Российской Федерации Я выбрал теперь
other side  superpowers and I felt
сторону другой сверхдержавы и я ощутил
this is what I was taught in childhood,
это то то чему меня учили в детстве вот
this is a superpower, it rings a menacing bell
это сверхдержава она Грозным колоколом
for everyone, that’s all And that Well, look
звонит по всем вот и всё И что Ну смотри
better, I mean your attitude
лучше же я имею в виду твоё отношение
in general to the world Well, to life there, to people,
вообще к миру Ну вот к жизни там к людям
and so on  for peace for the people because
и так Дале я за мир за людей потому что
as we say here By the way, Donald
как говорят у нас Вот кстати Дональд
Trump Yes, at his election speech in
Трамп Да он на своей предвыборной речи в
California he said that peace is not
Калифорнии сказал что мир - это не
the absence of war, peace is the absence of
отсутствие войны мира - это отсутствие
Moscow, a very interesting slogan was, well, that’s
Москвы очень интересный слоган был ну ну
it again.
это опять же Это ж
will tie you to but in Moscow people live, not
привяжет ко а Москве же живут люди не
different people, there are good ones, there are bad ones, yes
люди разные есть хорошие есть плохие да
Well, yes,
Ну да
there are good ones, there are bad ones, we don’t know
это есть хорошие есть плохие мы не знаем
who is good, who is bad, yes, the good ones, let
кто Хороший кто плохой Да хорошие Пусть
them leave Moscow, that’s all
выйдут из Москвы Вот и всё
nouveau. Well, for example, in Bakhmut, both
нува Ну например в бахмуте тоже жили и
good and bad people also lived, yes  Russia destroyed
хорошие и плохие да Россия уничтожила
Bakhmut, someone was worried in Russia, they were
бахмут кто-то переживал в России за это
n’t worried about it. Okay, in short, God is your
не переживал Ладно короче бо Бог тебе
judge, you’re not a judge, in our state of
судья ты не судья у нас у нас в штате
California, the judge is Peter Jackson. This is the
Калифорния судья Питер Джексон Вот это
judge. Peter Jackson is your judge. Yes Peter
судья Питер Джексон тебе судья Да Питер
Jackson Yes Jackson injection
Джексон Да Джексон инжекшен
Yes Jackson  Well, well, well, look, it’s
Да Джексон Ну теб Ну а что ну смотри
better. It would be better to be Yes, a
лучше Лучше бы лучше быть Да
representative of the people whose state
представителем народа чьё государство э
asserts its strong policy throughout the
утверждает свою сильную политику во всём
world. Than to be a representative of the Russian
мире Чем быть представителем Российской
Federation with which everyone laughs and about
Федерации с которой все смеются и об
which they wipe their feet and
которой вытирают ноги и санкции
impose sanctions, everyone laughs. But I think that
вводят все смеются Но я считаю что у
I have  A great power and in the World Cup. Great, you
меня Великая держава и в ЧМ Великая
understand, I could have been born a citizen of
понимаешь я я мог родиться гражданином
Burundi. And everyone would have laughed and been a
Бурунди Да и тоже бы все смеялись и быть
patriot instead of Well, okay, what is great about
патриотом а не Ну хорошо В чём велико
Russia
России твоей
and you were born in your own
а ты родился в своей
country And now yourself  Do you consider yourself a patriot of the
стране А сейчас себя считаешь патриотом
USA, what is great about your country? You
США сжи в чём велико твоей страны ты
chose a country that is there, yes Well,
выбрал себе страну которая там да Ну
maybe it is the strongest power,
может быть она самая сильная держава это
as you know, you are a weak person and took a
как знаешь ты вот слабый человек и взял
strong
себе сильного
satellite for yourself. And you were born Burundi, I sing your own, and
сателлита А ты родись Бурунди свою пою
Burundi is the strongest.
сжи Бурунди самая сильная
I am starting from a position of strength.  Because
Я исхожу из позиции силы Потому что
now my troops are on
сейчас мои войска находятся на
the territory of your country, your howl,
территории твоей страны твои вой твои
your troops, your parents live in Rostov.
войска У тебя родители в Ростове живут
That’s right, we’ll free them,
Правильно мы их освободим нормальную
they’ll get a normal pension. But I’ll
пенсию Бут
just go strong and tell you not to
просто пошл сильным и вс скажи ты не
maybe you said your country is Great
можеь ты сказал твоя страна Великая В
What is the greatness
чём величи
and in the World Cup the strength of your
а в ЧМ сила твоей
little dew So you invest your strength, look, the
росишки Так ты свою силу вложи смотри
ruble is O dollar already 105 105
рубль - это О доллар уже 105 105
rubles yes to yours Well, the USA in general, who are
руб да твоим Ну США вообще на тебя кто
you, what are you no no there are rights yes the
ты что ты нет нет есть права да
US Constitution Yes she  gives me the rights of a
конституция США Да она даёт мне права
citizen you are a stranger in this country with
гражданина ты чужой в этой стране
flags everything is here if you are a citizen
флагами тут все если ты гражданин
It doesn’t matter who is Irish Ukrainian Ru your
Неважно кто Ирландец украинец ру твоё
ethnic origin  where no one is
этническое происхождение отку никого не
interested in Biden Vaughn The Irishman
интересует байден вон Ирландец вообще
was in general What is clear So say in the World Cup What is
был Что понятно Так скажи в ЧМ В чём
your strength in your
твоя сила твоей
Russia damn it was to bomb the dude until the
России блин це было бомбить чувак до
last thought that he was communicating with the Rostovites
последнего думал что он с ростовцев
from America it was a bomb Who
общается из Америки это было бомба Кто
watches like subscribe comment this is the base and
смотрит лайк подписка коммент это база и
send it to everyone you know  it’s just such a
скиньте всем знакомым это просто такое
pathetic sight for him. I’ve
жалкое у него зрелище Я
already mocked him on the Right of the Strong how they
уже на Праве сильного издевался как они
graze in front of the Americans, it’s
пасут перед американцами это
funny write to my Telegram directly at the same time the
смешно пись на мий Telegram прямо зараз
VN axis but for
ось ВН а
now  so much more and more respectfully YouTube Zaga
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through skarg ODS in your ban and even
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people often I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams in order for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
Mali to write an operational link
того чтоб Мали оперативный звязок
right away and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim video sche tezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information  and we will blame you for the trimati
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
Nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава украини пись
with
с